# Yulia Penyevskaya

in/yuliapenyevskaya/ | Add portfolio URL | https://github.com/Yuliap21 | 646-617-4207 | yulia777best@gmail.com

### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

A bilingual Software Engineer with extensive experience in customer service. With a background in project, team, and time management, known for exceeding goals consistently. Self-driven and motivated by creating and executing new projects. Passionate about learning new technical skills and contributing to team initiatives.

#### **SKILLS**

Strong motivational skills | Highly Organized | Multi-tasker | High Energy | Positive Attitude | Problem Solving Bilingual - Fluent in Russian and English | MS Office | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe InDesign

## **TECHNICAL PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

# [Add GA projects here]

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Operation Manager | Matchpoint NYC | Brooklyn, NY

December 2013 -

- Present
  - Ensure quality control and workflow improvement by running all front desks in accordance with company protocol
  - Manage all customer requests and special situations across 3 locations
  - Oversee all front desk team supervision and training for 100+ team members and complete monthly performance reviews.
  - · Interview, recruit, hire, and train new people and manage schedules for multiple teams averaging just over 40 people
  - Coordinate seasonal tennis and basketball schedule preparation, payments, billing, and overtime
  - Maintain weekly, monthly, and annual financial reports and adjust statements, invoices, payroll and bill collection

Director of MultiSport Camp | Matchpoint Summer Camp Summer 2015, 2016, 2017

Managed camp enrollment, applications, and processing while maintaining activity schedules and hiring all trainers

CEO | Sweet21 Blossom | New York, NY

January 2016 - Present

- Created a cosmetic line business for professionals
- Researched and compared numerous products
- Sell product on platforms

Licensed Real Estate Sales Agent | Commercial Acquisitions Inc | Brooklyn, NY

March 2018 - March 2019

- Generated leads through various marketing campaigns including phone calls, email, and online ads
- Created legal documents including lease agreements, contracts, and deeds
- Consistently kept up to date with the local and national real estate market trends

Front Desk Receptionist | Revived Soul Medical Office | Brooklyn, NY

January 2012 - July 2014

- Provided exceptional customer service to all clients and patients
- Performed administrative duties including email correspondence, email composition, and phone and account monitoring

### **EDUCATION**

Software Engineering Immersive | General Assembly | Remote

April 2021 - October 2021

Business Administration | Kingsborough College | Brooklyn, NY

March 2016 - May 2018

Coursework in: Business Law, Business Fundamental, Communication class, Accounting

Interpreter/ Teacher of English and German | Kazan Pedagogical University | Kazan, Russia 2011

September 2008 - May

Graduated the course that included volunteering for 2 years as teachers assistant

Real Estate Course | Brooklyn, NY

September 2017- November

2018